Yeah. I use the telephone a lot.
Yeah.我电话打得很多.
As a matter of fact. my phone bill last month was like $125
事实上, 我上个月的电话费有125美元左右.
and that kind of freaked me out.
我都有点吓坏了,
so I thought maybe I should stop using the phone.
所以我想我也许不该再用电话了.
Er. at work I'm probably on the phone about 20 minutes an hour.
Er. 上班的时候我可能一个小时要打20分钟左右的电话,
um. both long distance and local.
um. 有长途的也有本地的.
and Actually.
事实上,
most of my friends are really busy and so we don't get to see each other a lot.
我大多数的朋友都非常忙, 平时不大见面,
so we spend a lot of time talking on the phone.
所以我们花很多时间在电话里交谈.
Sure. I do a lot of my business over the phone.
没错, 我常常在电话里谈生意.
Um. it's pretty important for getting in touch with people.
Um. 与别人保持联系是相当重要的.
I used to write a lot more letters.
我过去写信写得更多.
Now. probably. I call people up.
现在, 大多数情况下, 我就打电话了,
especially my brother in California,
尤其是打给我在加利福尼亚的兄弟,
and my parents in New York.
和在纽约的父母,
And at home I probably make a long distance call to friends around the country.
在家的时候我可能会给我在国内的朋友们打长途电话,
um. two or three times a week.
Um. 一星期两到三次吧,
and otherwise I'm probably on the phone 20 minutes. half an hour at night.
另外, 我可能会在晚上打20分钟, 半个小时的电话.
Yes. I mean I think you're a lot more purposeful when you get on the phone to talk business.
是的, 我的意思是说在电话里谈生意的目的性要强得多.
I mean. you have your questions all lined up.
我是说, 你需要问的问题都已列好,
you know what exactly you're looking for.
你知道你要的究竟是什么.
When you meet someone personally. you. er.
与人面对面交谈的时候,你, er.
you see body language
你看到他们的身体语言,
and you get a sense of how you're impacting them by what they say and what they think and how they look.
你可以从他们所说的话. 他们的想法以及他们的表情中感觉到你对他们的影响.
But when you talk to someone on the phone.
但是, 在电话里与人交谈的时候,
you have to really listen much more carefully. I think.
你就得更加认真仔细地听对方所说的话, 我觉得.
In some ways.
从某些方面来说.
maybe the phone can be even more intimate than when you meet.
在电话里交谈也许会比面对面的交谈更亲密一些.
A couple of other features.
电话还有其他几个特点,
er. if. er. a call comes in.
er. 如果. er. 有个电话进来了,
obviously answering machines which will take the call when you're not there.
很显然, 电话应答机在你不在的时候就会替你接电话.
but if you just miss a call.
不过, 如果你没有接到某个电话,
you can dial star and then 69
你可以先拨星号, 再拨69.
and it'll call back whomever just called you.
这样你就可以回电话给刚才那个打电话给你的人.
Five or ten years ago. I remember how uncomfortable people were talking into machines and it's been.
5到I0年前, 我记得人们觉得对着机器说话特别不自在,
it's really interesting to see that it's gone from people talking to machines to really feel like.
但有趣的是, 人们不再觉得是在和机器说话.
feeling like they're actually communicating with the person.
感觉就像自己的确是在与人交谈.